Finding aid for the John Fahey papers LSC.1862
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 2. International Travel, 1983-2001
  - China, HIV/AIDS in China and postdoctoral program, 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Thailand, 1995-2002 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Vietnam, 1994-1999 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Japan, 1983-1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Australia, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - China, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - China, AIDS talk, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- 3. Training Manuals, 1978-2001
  This series contains training manuals for medical professionals on HIV/AIDS, reference guides for AIDS and other immunologic diseases, as well as training program documents for UCLA's Medical Laboratory Immunology.
  - Medical Laboratory Immunology (MLI) organization and training program, 1982, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Medical Lab Immunology training program, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - AIDS/HIV, Reference Guide for Medical Professionals, Third Edition (CIRID), eds. Diana M. Shin and JoAnne Avers, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - AIDS Reference Guide for Medical Professionals, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Lecture slides, Idiopathic CD4+ T lymphocytopenia (ICL) and cluster of differentiation 4 (CD4), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Center for International Research in Immunology and Disease (CIRID) brochures and dedication, 1979 May 4 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research in Immunologic Disease (CIRID), overview, 1985 and 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research in Immunologic Disease (CIRID), description of space, 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research in Immunologic Disease (CIRID), overview, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research in Immunologic Disease (CIRID), resources and environment, 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research in Immunologic Disease (CIRID) and Clinical Immunology Research Laboratories, correspondence and reports, 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research in Immunologic Diseases (CIRID) Volume I, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Research in Immunologic Diseases (CIRID) Volume II, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - AIDS Reference Guide For Medical Professionals, First Edition, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - AIDS Reference Guide For Medical Professionals, Second Edition, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - UCLA Center for Interdisciplinary Research in Immunology and Disease (CIRID), Directory, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Immunology and AIDS pamphlets, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Latinos and AIDS, A National Strategy Symposium (CIRID), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - AIDS/HIV Infection, A Reference Guide for Nursing Professionals, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - HIV/AIDS, A Guide to Primary Care Management, Fourth Edition, eds. Jacquelyn Haak Flaskerud and Peter Ungvarski, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Inscription on first page from Jackie Flaskerud (editor)
  - HIV/AIDS, A Guide to Nursing Care, Third Edition, eds. Jacquelyn Haak Flaskerud and Peter Ungvarski, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Inscription on first page from Jackie Flaskerud (Editor)
  - AIDS/HIV, Reference Guide for Medical Professionals, 4th Edition (CIRID), eds. John L. Fahey and Diana Shin Fleming, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- 4. India, 1970-2009
  This series contains primarily correspondence and documentation related to collaborations, research and training programs in India. Included are grant applications, memoranda and program information, biographical sketches for scholars, information on contemporary research and training/program outlines and budgets.
  - Approach to Clinical Research Workshop, 2009 January 21-24 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - International Clinical, Operational and Health Services Research and Training Award (ICOHRTA), summary statement and proposal, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - India Council of Medical Research, Vishwa Mohan Katoch correspondence, 1998-2008 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Chennai and Madras - Tamil Nadu (articles), 2009 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Visa application and information, 1970, 1998, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - UCLA presentations, Dr. Anbumani Ramadoss, 2008 June 25 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence regarding All India Institute of Medical Sciences (AIIMS), New Delhi, and CIRID, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence regarding participation in the International Conference on HIV/AIDS, New Delhi, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Various correspondence regarding Fogarty and International Conference on AIDS India, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - UCLA International Research Policy, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Visit from Dr. A. Ramadoss, Minister of Health and Family Welfare, 2008 June 25 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Microbicides 2008 Conference, New Delhi, 2008 February 23-37 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - India Council of Medical Research, correspondence, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - National AIDS Research Institute, proposal for joint Bilateral UCLA-ICMR development, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Bryson, Nyamathi, Tamanoi, Application for Nanotechnology and Transdisciplinary Approaches to Global Health Issues Facing Children and their Families, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Training and workshops for treatment and prevention of HIV/AIDS, correspondence and research on comorbidity, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Y.K. Gupta correspondence, AIDS International Training and Research Program (AITRP), 2007-2009 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Maulana Azad Medical College (MAMC), AIDS Physicians Training, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Bilateral training application, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Center for International Research in Immunology and Disease conference on AIDS, 2007 March 1 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - India Council of Medical Research, correspondence with Vishwa Mohan Katoch, 1998-2007 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - General Clinical Research Centers Program (GCRC), 2008 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Nanotechnology, Leonard Rome, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - UNESCO Regional Centre for Education & Training in Biotechnology at Faridabad, Haryana, 2008 May (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - UCLA Department of Biotechnology, UNESCO Center, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - S. Sinha, Department of Biotechnology, visit, 2007 July (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) between UCLA and Indian Council of Medical Research, 2007 October (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Dr. S. Anuradha correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Department of Biotechnology, Biotech magazine, 2008 December (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - King George Medical University, 2005-2008 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - S. Sinha, Department of Biotechnology correspondence, 2006-2008 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - A.K. Singh, Minister of State for Health & Family Welfare, visit, 2007 September 16-19 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Altaf Lal, Paolo Miotti correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - 7th Asia-Pacific Congress of Medical Virology, All India Institute of Medical Sciences, 2006 November (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Fogarty Global Health Matters, Millennium Promise Awards, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Seventh Sir Dorabji Tata Symposium - HIV/AIDS Research Issues in Bangalore, 2006 March (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - All India Institute of Medical Sciences (AIIMS) visit, 2006 January (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Global Impact of AIDS talk, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Tina Wu, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - AIDS talks, activities in India, 2004-2007 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Global Impact of HIV/AIDS, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence regarding All India Institute of Medical Sciences nursing training and programs, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 5th Indo-US Behavioral HIV Workshop, Bangalore, 2006 February 12-15 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - AIDS in India information and expanding access to treatment, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Continuing Medical Education (CME)-Antiretroviral Treatment (ART), 2005 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Gathering of UCLA-AITRP Fellows in Chennai, 2005 October 20-23 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Central Council for Research in Ayurveda and Siddha, Golden Triangle, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Tuberculosis control in India, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Institute for Clinical Research India, New Delhi and Chennai, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Clinton Foundation, correspondence and program information, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - UCLA programs and collaborations in India, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - AIDS/India working group, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - AIDS in India think tank, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - AIDS in India program, UCLA AIDS Institute, white paper, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - AIDS in India program, AIDS Institute, white paper, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth Simpson, NIH, correspondence regarding establishment of clinical research center, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - UCLA Lab science, Department of Biotechnology, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Travel to Pune and Chennai, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - AIDS in India working group, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Society of India, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Knowledge translation, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - UCLA Training for Clinical Research, fellowship program, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - US Embassy, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - General correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence and notes, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Chennai and Madras articles, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Visa application and information, 1970, 1998, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - National Institute of Immunology annual report, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - American Association of Immunologists newsletter, 2007 December (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Federation of Clinical Immunology Societies (FOCIS) Immunology Meeting, 2007 June 8-9 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - 14th Conference on Retroviruses and Opportunistic Infections, email, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Acceptance for Asian-Pacific Congress of Medical Virology, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - VII Symposium on HIV/AIDS Research Issues, correspondence, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - 4th Annual Cytokines and Inflammation, correspondence, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - International Seminar on Chronic Diseases and its Management by Complementary and Alternative Medicine, program and email, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Round Table Conference HIV and Tuberculosis, New Delhi, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Visit of AIIMS Faculty to UCLA, email and itinerary, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Travel correspondence for Continuing Medical Education, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - XV International AIDS Conference, Bangkok, correspondence, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Business cards, notes, email, 2004 February (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - 11th Conference on Retroviruses and Opportunistic Infections registration correspondence, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Travel to India correspondence, 2004 January (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Assessment of Future Developments of Immune Based Therapies in HIV Infection workshop, itineraries and correspondence, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Travel correspondence for workshops in India, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - 4th International Conference on AIDS, Chennai, India, 2003 November 9-12 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 2nd IAS Conference on HIV Treatment and Pathogenesis, Paris, attendance, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Travel itinerary, 2003 April (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Travel itinerary, 2003 January (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Travel itinerary, 2002 September (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Travel itinerary and correspondence for Fogarty International Center's AIDS Programs update in Barcelona, 2002 July (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Clinical Immunology Societies (FOCiS) 2nd Annual Meeting, San Francisco, 2002 June (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Visit to NIH for UCLA Fogarty AITRP India Studies, 2002 May (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Visit to New Delhi, 2002 February (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Visit to India, correspondence regarding activities UCLA is involved in in India, 2001 September (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence regarding participation in the International Conference on HIV/AIDS, 2001 December (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Various correspondence regarding Fogarty and International Conference on AIDS India, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - 6th International Conference on AIDS in Asia and the Pacific, Melbourne, Australia, 2001 October (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - University-wide AIDS Research Program Task Force, program information, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Psychoneuroimmunology (PNI) Research Society meeting, Netherlands, 2001 May 16-19 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Federation of Clinical Immunology Societies (FOCiS) Annual Meeting, Boston, 2001 May (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Visit to India for the Federation of Immunological Societies of Asia-Oceania course on Immunology, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - National Institute of Epidemiology, Chennai, 2001 February (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence regarding collaborations between UCLA and Indian AIDS researchers, Dallas Swendeman, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence with Peter Anton regarding research, programs and collaborations in India, 2004-2008 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - UCLA-India Translational Health Sciences Research and Training Program (THSRTP), 2008 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Fogarty Strategic Plan, 2008-2012 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Pushing an India-agenda in the Health Sciences at UCLA, correspondence and program organization, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - UCLA Clinical and Translational Science Institute training in India, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - UCLA Clinical and Translational Sciences Institute (CTSI) Conference, Clinical Research Education & Specialized Training (CREST) committee, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - UCLA Clinical and Translational Sciences Institute (CTSI) general information, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Martin Shapiro, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Thomas Rosenthal, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence regarding Isidro Salusky, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - UCLA-India program and correspondence with Jeff Miller, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Mitsuyasu, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence with Carol Mangione, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - UCLA-India Program review, Roger Detels, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Central Council for Research in Homeopathy (CCRH)-UCLA Collaborative Study for HIV Prevention in India, program and correspondence, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Neil Wenger, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence with David Heber regarding nutrition, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Institutional Clinical and Translational Award program information, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Evaluation and Outcome Measures, Translational Research Group, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Memorandum of Understanding Between UCLA and the Indian Council of Medical Research, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - UCLA International Institute Agreement Review Sheet, Memorandum of Understanding between UCLA and Indian Council of Medical Research, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Includes picture of Jeff Miller
  - Memorandum of Understanding, Indian Council of Medical Research, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - NIH/Ken Bridbord correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Visit from University of California President, Robert Dynes, and UCLA-India initiative, correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Department of Biotechnology collaborations/programs in India, correspondence and information, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence regarding a visit from Dr. Sheela Godbole, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Global Research Initiative Program (GRIP) for New Foreign Investigators, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Naveet Wig, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - International Clinical, Operational and Health Services Research and Training Award (ICOHRTA), summary statement and proposal, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Naveet Wig regarding International Clinical, Operational and Health Services Research and Training Award (ICOHRTA), 2006 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - All India Institute of Medical Sciences, general information and correspondence, 2006-2009 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - India Phase II Comprehensive ICOHRTA AIDS/TB Program grant application, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence with Naveet Wig regarding San Diego meeting, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - AIDS in India data, correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - UCLA School of Public Health information and information on growth of AIDS in India, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Institute of Health Management Research training, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Narendra K. Akora, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence with Rajat Ray, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence with Chandra Pandav, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Kanchan Mukherjee and Tata Institute of Social Sciences, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - National AIDS Control Program Phase III, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence with Thomas Nutman, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - International Clinical, Operational, and Health Services Research Training Award AIDS/TB Grant information and correspondence, 2003-2006 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - International Clinical, Operational, and Health Services Research Training Award II summary statement, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - International Clinical, Operational, and Health Services Research Training Award II, critique and correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Alan Robinson, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with S.K. Sharma, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - All India Institute of Medical Sciences HIV/TB research, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with and articles by Narinder Mehra, 1998-2009 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Pradeep Seth, 2005-2009 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Pradeep Seth biographical data and publications list, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence regarding Pradeep Seth and development of AIDS vaccine, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to and regarding Jyotish Samantaray, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Lecture slide print outs about AIDS research and implementation of programs, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - AIDS in India, review and scope of UCLA programs, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - All India Institute of Medical Sciences AIIMSonians of America convention, vaccine science, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - All India Institute of Medical Sciences Drug Dependence Treatment Center summary of research, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Narendra Arora, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Sushil Kumar Kabra, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Ashutosh Biswas, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Rajat Ray and regarding research programs in India, 2003-2005 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Global AIDS, Therapeutics Research Education AIDS Training (TREAT), needs for training, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - HIV/AIDS treatment and prevention in India, World Bank, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Ethical Guidelines for Biomedical Research on Human Subjects, ICMR, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - The Future of AIDS talk, Nicholas Eberstadt, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Emerging areas of operational research in India, articles, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Various articles on HIV/AIDS in India and globally, 2001-2005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Office of AIDS Research (OAR), Correspondence with Jack Whitescarver, 2004 June 4 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Department of Biotechnology -- Translational Health Sciences Research Education and Training Program, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Department of Biotechnology -- Translational Health Sciences Research for HIV/AIDS concept proposal, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Department of Biotechnology -- Fundamental Biomedical Sciences Training Programs proposal, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Department of Biotechnology -- Clinical Research Training Program grant, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Department of Biotechnology -- Clinical Research Training program, collaboration with UCLA, 2006-2008 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Department of Biotechnology -- correspondence with Naveet Wig and S. Sinha, 2008-2009 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - NIH Application for Supplemental Award for UCLA programs in India, 2008-2009 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Martin Shapiro regarding programs in India, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Naveet Wig regarding programs in India, 2008-2009 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Department of Biotechnology -- Defense Ministry link correspondence, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with Sushil Kumar Kabra regarding UCLA-AIIMS collaboration, 2007-2009 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Colleagues -- correspondence with Soumya Swaminathan, 2003-2009 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Colleagues -- correspondence with Kaustuv Nayak, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Colleagues -- correspondence with P.R. Naraynan, 2003-2005 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Colleagues -- Beena Thomas, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Colleagues -- correspondence with Padmapriya Darsini, 2006-2009 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Colleagues -- correspondence with Padmapriya Darsini, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Colleagues -- correspondence with Eric Chamot, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Colleagues -- correspondence with Thomas Nutman, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Colleagues -- correspondence with M. Suresh Kumar, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Colleagues -- correspondence regarding National Institute of Epidemiology, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Colleagues -- correspondence with Mohan Gupte, 2002-2009 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Department of AYUSH, quality of life, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Department of AYUSH, concept paper, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Narrative Prevention Counseling for STI/HIV Prevention, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Colleagues -- correspondence with Anil Kumar Khurana, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Alternative Medicine/HIV lecture slides and articles by Bette Chang, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Traditional Medicine articles, 2002-2008 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Complimentary and Alternative Medicine, 2002-2005 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- 5. UCLA Institutes, 1972-2009
  This series contains program information, budget information, building plans and studies conducted by UCLA Institutes. Included are biographical sketches of researchers, meeting minutes and agendas, proposals for research, personal financial information and various documents on Immunological research.
  - UCLA Immunology Center -- program information and affiliation to other UCLA programs, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - UCLA Immunology Center -- historiographical information, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - UCLA Immunology Center -- planning and strategy, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - UCLA Immunology Center -- program proposal, outline, outreach and education, and correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - UCLA Immunology Center -- planning, correspondence, meeting agendas and faculty listing, 1983-1985 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - UCLA Immunology Center -- planning committee agendas, notes and organizational structure, 1986-1988 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - UCLA Immunology Center -- planning committee minutes, agendas, program, 1987-1989 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Lifetime achievement celebration for John Fahey in Clinical Immunology Spectrum, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Clinical Immunology Research Laboratory (CIRL) -- expenses and reports, 2000-2002 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Clinical Immunology Research Laboratory (CIRL) -- summary, memorandum, publications list and biographical sketches, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Clinical Immunology Research Laboratory (CIRL) -- revision in computer system, flow cytometry survey, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Clinical Immunology Research Laboratory (CIRL) -- correspondence regarding progress of CIRL and award nomination form, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)